(Penny:)- Sheldon.
- Ugh. Sorry.
Boy, we gotta get you into a better office.
Something more suited to your status.
- You don't have to go to trouble.
- How about von Gerlach's old office?
- I'd rather have Fishbein's. It's bigger.
GABLEHAUSER: Done.
Wait, I called dibs on Fishbein's office...
(Howard:)...the day he started showing up at work
in his bathrobe.
He gets a new office, I can't get
paper towels in the men's room?
(Penny:)- Sheldon.
- Damn, this is hard.
Let me ask you, what do you think
the business of this place is?
[WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
- Science?
- Money.
(Howard:)Told you.
(Gablehauser:)And this boy's picture
in People magazine...
...is gonna raise us
a pile of money taller than...
(Gablehauser:)Well, taller than you.
- I have a master's degree.
- Who doesn't?